African American Soldiers in World War II Collection
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
African American Soldiers in World War II Collection 1918-2018 1997-2010
MSS86243
7,000 items
20 containers
8.0 linear feet
3,170 digital files (118.23 GB)
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Correspondence, memoranda, oral history interviews, government documents, reports, notes, books, subject files, a scrapbook, photographs, newspaper clippings, printed matter, digital files, and other material documenting the World War II participation of African American soldiers of the 92nd and 93rd Infantry Divisions of the United States Army.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Adams, Susan (Non-commissioned officer)--Interviews.; Lane, Madine Davis, 1919-2015--Interviews.; Morehouse, Maggi M., 1953- Fighting in the Jim Crow Army: black men and women remember World War II. 2000.; Morehouse, Maggi M., 1953- Maggi M. Morehouse papers.; Quarterman, Lee Sinclair, 1914-1991 Lee Sinclair Quarterman military records and photographs.
Organizations
United States. Army--African American troops.; United States. Army. Dental Corps.; United States. Army. Infantry Division, 92nd.; United States. Army. Infantry Division, 93rd.; United States. Servicemen's Readjustment Act of 1944.
Subjects
African American soldiers.; African American veterans--Education.; African American veterans--Employment.; African American veterans--Interviews.; African American veterans.; African Americans--Civil rights.; African Americans--Segregation.; African Americans--Social conditions--20th century.; Civil rights movements--United States.; Civil rights--United States.; Race discrimination--United States.; Race relations.; Veterans' families--Interviews.; Veterans--Education--Law and legislation--United States.; Veterans--Education--United States.; Veterans--Legal status, laws, etc.--United States.; Veterans--United States.; World War, 1939-1945--Europe.; World War, 1939-1945--Medical care.; World War, 1939-1945--Pacific Area.; World War, 1939-1945--Participation, African American.; World War, 1939-1945--Participation, Female.; World War, 1939-1945--United States.; World War, 1939-1945--Veterans--United States--Economic conditions.; World War, 1939-1945--Veterans--United States--Social conditions.; World War, 1939-1945--Veterans--United States.
Places
Fort Benning (Ga.)--History.; Fort Bragg (N.C.)--History.; Fort Huachuca (Ariz.)--History.; United States--Armed Forces--African Americans.; United States--Armed Forces--Women.; United States--Race relations.; United States--Social conditions--20th century.; United States--Social conditions--21st century.
Acquisition Information
The African American Soldiers in World War II Collection was given to the Library of Congress by Maggi M. Morehouse in 2018.
Transfers
Audiotapes and videotapes have been transferred to the Motion Picture, Broadcasting and Recorded Sound Division where they are identified as part of the African American Soldiers in World War II Collection.
Related Material
Related collections in the Manuscript Division include the papers of Eugene E. Johnston and the records of the United States Army 92nd Infantry Division Collection (see https://hdl.loc.gov/loc.mss/eadmss.ms008096).
Access and Restrictions
The African American Soldiers in World War II Collection is open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Some interview recordings were received by the Library without documentation granting release of the interview. Access may be limited as a result. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room for more information.
Technical Requirements
Digital files were created in a Windows operating system, version is unknown. The content is primarily audio files in .wav format and moving image files in .VOB format.
Organizational History
The 92nd Infantry Division and the 93rd Infantry Division were racially segregated units of the United States Army during World War I and World War II. Nicknamed the "Buffalo Soldier Division," the 92nd was the only African American division in World War II to see combat in Europe as part of the Fifth Army. The 93rd Division, known as the "Blue Helmet" Division, acquired that sobriquet when the division fought in France in World War I. The 93rd Division served in combat in the Pacific Theater during World War II.
Scope and Content Note
The African American Soldiers in World War II Collection spans the years 1918-2018, with the bulk of the collection dating from 1997 to 2010. It consists of correspondence, memoranda, oral history interview transcripts, reports, government documents, books, notes, photographs, articles, maps, a scrapbook, newspaper clippings, printed matter, digital files, and other material utilized by Maggi M. Morehouse to document the service primarily of two African American combat divisions in World War II, the 92nd and 93rd Infantry Divisions of the United States Army. The 92nd Infantry Division saw heavy combat during the Italian campaign from 1944 to 1945. The 93rd Division was reactivated in 1942 at Fort Huachuca, Arizona, and served in the Pacific Theater chiefly in construction work and in combat support positions. The collection is in English and is arranged into four groups: interviews and related material, Maggi M. Morehouse's personal file, subject files, and digital files.
Morehouse began researching the service of Black soldiers in World War II in 1995 for a graduate history seminar. She continued to study the topic for her master's thesis and dissertation which later became a book titled Fighting in the Jim Crow Army: Black Men and Women Remember World War II. She has written a number of articles and papers about the subject. This collection documents her research using secondary sources and primary sources. The topic also had a personal connection for Morehouse because her father, Lee Sinclair Quarterman, served as a white officer in the 93rd Infantry Division.
Almost one half the collection is comprised of interviews by Morehouse with World War II veterans. The interview files include transcripts, correspondence, government documents, notes, photographs, unit histories, newspaper articles, and other material relating to the individual interviewed. Although both the 92nd and 93rd divisions were trained for battle, many of the men were assigned non-combat duties. Some of the training locales mentioned are Fort Bragg, North Carolina, Fort Benning, Georgia, and Fort Huachuca, Arizona. In the interviews the soldiers describe what it was like to serve in a segregated army and the racial attitudes they encountered at home and abroad. They describe life before and after the army. Serving in the military allowed the soldiers to experience the world outside their segregated communities and to obtain an education using the G. I. Bill. As a result many became part of the middle class and were active in the civil rights movement during the 1950s and 1960s.
Represented in the interviews are two women veterans, Susan Adams, who served in Germany in the Army Dental Corps, and Madine Davis Lane, who served as a nurse at Fort Huachuca, and in the China Burma India Theater, Egypt, Europe, and Okinawa. Some interviews include the participation of a soldier's spouse, and a few interviews consist solely of children discussing their father's military service. Filed at the beginning of the interviews are alphabetical lists of the soldiers interviewed by Morehouse. The lists also include a brief synopsis of the interview. One of the lists noted that there was an interview of Morehouse's father in the interview files. The Library, however, did not receive it. Quarterman's interview file does contain extensive military papers about his service and some original photographs of him. Additional interviewees include Hattie Mae Settles Allen, William S. M. Banks, Ogelsby B. Barrett, J. Herman Blake, Albert Burke, Leonard Cunningham, Roland Dix, Ruth Earl, Howard Fletcher, Arthur Goodwin, Felix Goodwin, Allen E. Green, Anna Hairston, Joseph Hairston, Charles Hanson, Dennette Arthur Harrod, Arnett Hartsfield, Cleather Hathcock, Howard Hickerson, Levi Hill, Reuben Horner, Jehu Callis Hunter, Fred L. Hurns, Ezell Jackson, Niani Kilkenny, Lawrence Johnson, Charles Lancaster, Robert P. Madison, Mick Marshall, John B. Mathews, William C. McCullough, Dorothy McIver, I. P. McIver, Thomas McKinney, Cullen McKissock, Donald McNeil, Harold Montgomery, Helen Montgomery, Spencer Moore, Susie Moore, William H. Payne, Nelson Peery, A. William Perry, Matthew J. Perry, Alex Pitcher, Edward Price, Joseph L. Stephenson, Thomas P. Stoney, Allen Thompson, W. E. ("Burg") Turner, Woodrow Walton, Fred Watt, Charles Wesly, Edgar Whitley, Clyde Whitted, Henry L. ("Hank") Williams, and Jim Williams.
Morehouse's personal file features her correspondence with veterans and research institutions pertaining to her research, her presentations, and writings about African Americans' participation in World War II, particularly her dissertation and book, and her work on an exhibit and book project entitled A War on Two Fronts: Fighting for Victory at Home and Abroad. Also included is a scrapbook relating to Morehouse's father that features government documents, family papers, and photographs pertaining to his army career.
The subject files provide further documentation of Morehouse's research and include files about African American history, military units, and the integration of the armed forces. Subject files featured are the 93rd Infantry Division and Fort Huachuca, Arizona, and the Buffalo Soldiers (92nd Infantry Division). The nickname Buffalo Soldiers was given by Native Americans to African American cavalrymen who served in the American West in the nineteenth century. The most comprehensive files are those about Fort Huachuca and the Buffalo Soldiers. Most of the photographs are copies from the 1940s. Photographs from the 1990s and 2000s mainly document reunions of the veterans.
The digital files mainly consist of audio and video files of interviews conducted by Morehouse with veterans. In some cases, recordings are incomplete or include distorted audio. Also included in the digital files are materials relating to the subject file and Morehouse's writings.
Arrangement of the Papers
This collection is arranged alphabetically by type of material and therein alphabetically.
Container List
- Interviews and related material (Box 1)
  - Consent forms and related material 1998, 2007-2010 (Box 1)
  - Lists, 2017-2018 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Susan, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Allen, Hattie Mae Settles, 2008 (Box 1)
  - Banks, William S. M., 1943-1949, 1960-1965, 1995-1997 (Box 1)
  - Barrett, Ogelsby B., 1998 (Box 1)
  - Blake, J. Herman, 1994, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Burke, Albert, 1998, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Cunningham, Leonard, 2008 (Box 1)
  - Dix, Roland, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Earl, Ruth, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Fletcher, Howard, 2010 (Box 1)
  - Goodwin, Arthur, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Goodwin, Felix, 1993-1998, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Green, Allen E., 1998 (Box 2)
  - Hairston, Anna, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Hairston, Joseph, 1946, 1998-1999, 2010, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Hanson, Charles, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - Harrod, Dennette Arthur, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Hartsfield, Arnett, 1997-1999 (Box 2)
  - Hathcock, Cleather, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Hickerson, Howard, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Hill, Levi, 1984, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Horner, Reuben, 1969, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Hunter, Jehu Callis, 1985-1988, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Hurns, Fred L., 1945, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Jackson, Ezell, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Johnson, Lawrence, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Lancaster, Charles, 2010 (Box 3)
  - Lane, Madine Davis, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Madison, Robert P., 1998 (Box 3)
  - Marshall, Mick, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Mathews, John B., 2005 (Box 3)
  - McCullough, William C., 1998 (Box 3)
  - McIver, Dorothy and I. P., 1998 (Box 3)
  - McKinney, Thomas, 1998 (Box 3)
  - McKissock, Cullen, 1998 (Box 3)
  - McNeil, Donald, undated (Box 4)
  - Montgomery, Harold and Helen, 1997, 2006 (Box 4)
  - Montgomery, Helen, and Niani Kilkenny (daughter), 2010 (Box 4)
  - Moore, Spencer and Susie, 1944-1945, 1988-1998, 2008-2010, (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - Payne, William H., 1995-1999, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Peery, Nelson, 1943-1952, 1992-1999, 2015-2018, (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - Perry, A. William, 1942-1950, 1998-1999, 2007-2014, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Perry, Matthew J., 2004, 2010-2014 (Box 5)
  - Pitcher, Alex, 1997-1998 (Box 5)
  - Price, Edward, 1938, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Quarterman, Lee Sinclair, 1943-1951, 1994-2003, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Stephenson, Joseph L., 1998, 2010-2012 (Box 6)
  - Stoney, Thomas P., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Thompson, Allen, 1998, undated (Box 6)
  - Turner, W. E. ("Burg"), 1998 (Box 6)
  - Walton, Woodrow, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Watt, Fred, 1945-1946, 1998-2000 (Box 6)
  - Wesly, Charles, 1998, undated (Box 6)
  - Whitley, Edgar, 1998-2001, undated (Box 6)
  - Whitted, Clyde, 1998, undated (Box 6)
  - Williams, Henry L. ("Hank"), 1987-2005, (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Williams, Jim, 1998 (Box 7)
- Morehouse, Maggi M., personal file (Box 7)
  - African American Museum and Library at Oakland, Oakland, Calif., 1995 (Box 7)
  - Books for research, 1943-1945, 1975, 1994-2014 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, 1992-2017, (3 folders) (Box 7)
  - German Historical Institute, Washington, D.C., 1998, 2014, undated (Box 7)
  - Library of Congress, 2015-2017 (Box 7)
  - Museums, 1995, undated (Box 7)
  - National Archives and Records Administration, Washington, D.C., 1996, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Notes, interviews, 1996-1997, 2004-2007, (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Notes, writing and research, 1995-2000, 2017, (5 folders) (Box 8)
  - Port Chicago Mutiny, Port Chicago, Calif., 1996, 2014 (Box 8)
  - Presentations, 2001-2017, (2 folders) (Box 8)
  - Scrapbook, 1940-1950, 1995-2004, (2 folders) (Box 9)
  - U. S. Army Military History Institute, Carlisle, Pa., 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - Veterans (Box 9)
    - Correspondence and newspaper clippings, 1997-2008 (Box 9)
    - Huachucan Veterans Association, Cleveland, Ohio, 1992-2011, (3 folders) (Box 9)
    - Photographs, 1995-2015, (5 folders); (2 folders) (Box 9, Box 10)
  - Writings (Box 10)
    - "Black Citizen Soldiers" (dissertation), 2001, (4 folders) (Box 10)
    - Fighting in the Jim Crow Army: Black Men and Women Remember World War II (book), 2000 (Box 10)
    - "The Long Civil Rights Movement" (essay), undated, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Rowman and Littlefield, Inc., 1997-2010, (3 folders) (Box 11)
    - Various articles and papers (Box 11)
      - 1994-2008, (4 folders) (Box 11)
      - 2009-2016, (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - A War on Two Fronts: Fighting for Victory at Home and Abroad (exhibit and book), 2012-2016, (6 folders) (Box 12)
    - "War Stories: Personal Battles of Black Soldiers in World War II" (master's thesis), 1998 (Box 13)
- Subject file (Box 13)
  - 24th Infantry Division, 1986 (Box 13)
  - 25th Infantry Division, 1933-1942, undated (Box 13)
  - 93rd Infantry Division (Box 13)
    - Christmas menu and program, 1941 (Box 13)
    - Conference papers, dissertation, and thesis, 1992-1997, (2 folders) (Box 13)
    - Government documents, 1943-1946, 1959, 1980-1987, (3 folders) (Box 13)
    - Map, 2000 (Box 13)
    - Newspaper clippings and printed matter, 1942, 1972-1975, 1984, 1999-2000 (Box 13)
    - Photographs (mainly photocopies), 1942-1945 (Box 13)
  - 350th Field Artillery Battalion, undated (Box 13)
  - 368th Infantry Division, 1942 (Box 13)
  - 369th Infantry Division, 1944-1946, 1991 (Box 13)
  - 370th Infantry Division, 1944-1945 (Box 13)
  - 643rd Port Company Transportation Corps, undated (Box 13)
  - African Americans (Box 14)
    - General history (Box 14)
      - Almanac reference sheets, undated (Box 14)
      - Articles, 1983, 2004-2017, (2 folders) (Box 14)
      - Audio and video material, 1984, 1990, 2010, undated (Box 14)
      - Books 1975-1984, 1993-1997, 2006-2011, (4 folders) (Box 14)
      - Fact sheets, 1991-1995 (Box 14)
      - Government documents, 1942-1945, 1985, 1993, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 14, Box 15)
      - Magazines, 1943, 1984-1999, (2 folders) (Box 15)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1994-2000 (Box 15)
      - Oral histories, 1995-1999, 2009-2010 (Box 15)
      - Programs, 1943, 1997 (Box 15)
      - Statistics, surveys, and studies, 1942, 1965-1966, 1990, 2005-2006 (Box 15)
    - Society (Box 15)
      - Articles, journals, and a book review, 1987-2008 (Box 15)
      - Correspondence, 1996, undated (Box 15)
      - Government documents, 1942-1945, (2 folders) (Box 15)
      - Magazines, 1982, 1998-1999 (Box 15)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1942, 1995-2004 (Box 16)
      - Photograph, photocopy, undated (Box 16)
      - Racial situation reports, 1944-1945, (3 folders) (Box 16)
  - "Battles and captures," 1995-1997, 2005-2008 (Box 16)
  - Camp Patrick Henry, Va., 1944 (Box 16)
  - Cemeteries and monuments, undated (Box 16)
  - Fort Huachuca, Ariz., and the Buffalo Soldiers (Box 16)
    - Books, 1921, 1943-1969, 1985-1998, (4 folders) (Box 16)
    - "The Buffalo" (newsletter), 1994-2002, 2010-2012 (Box 16)
    - Buildings (Box 17)
      - General, 1986, undated (Box 17)
      - Historic preservation, 2004-2013 (Box 17)
    - Conference paper and almanac, 1959, 1992 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1945, 1971, 1999 (Box 17)
    - First day covers, 1994 (Box 17)
    - Flyers, 1996, undated (Box 17)
    - General history, 2001-2002, undated (Box 17)
    - Government documents, 1941-1948, 1970-1972, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Huachuca Illustrated, 1993-1996, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Magazine articles, 1944, 1981-2000, 2008 (Box 17)
    - Maps, 1995-2000, undated (Box 17)
    - Memorial and cemetery, 1997, undated (Box 18)
    - Military propaganda, photocopies, 1944-1945 (Box 18)
    - Newspaper articles, 1942-1945, 1983-1984, 1995-1996, 2004, (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Ninety-Second Infantry Division World War II Association 1982, 2009 (Box 18)
    - Photographs, 1918, 1932-1945, 1994, (3 folders) (Box 18)
    - Reunions (Box 18)
      - Photographs, 1990, 1998, 2007, undated (Box 18)
      - General, 1991-2014, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Song lyrics, 1943 (Box 18)
    - Video and audio, 2002, 2008-2010 (Box 18)
  - Germany, 2008-2009 (Box 19)
  - G. I. Bill, 1944, 1962 (Box 19)
  - Integration of the armed forces (Box 19)
    - Articles, 1998-2010 (Box 19)
    - Books, 1950, 1962-1963, 1977-1980, 1992-1995, (2 folders) (Box 19)
    - Chronologies, 2008 (Box 19)
    - Government documents, 1945-1948, 1985-1997, 2008-2010, (3 folders) (Box 19)
    - Journals, 1954, 1992-1993, 2005-2007 (Box 19)
    - Magazines, newspapers, and other media, 1943-1944, 1985, 1995-2009 (Box 19)
    - Reports, 1947 (Box 20)
  - Medals of honor, 1982, 1995-1998, 2008 (Box 20)
  - Movies, 1997-1998, 2007-2008 (Box 20)
  - Native Americans, 1945 (Box 20)
  - Obituaries, 1995-1999, 2008-2010 (Box 20)
  - Pacific Theater (Box 20)
    - Books, 1945-1953, 1969, 1988-1991, (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Correspondence, 1944, 1999 (Box 20)
    - Government documents, 1944-1945 (Box 20)
    - Maps, 1944, undated (Box 20)
    - Newspapers and journals, 1974-1975, 1988, 1995, 2006 (Box 20)
    - Oral histories, 1999 (Box 20)
  - Tank battalions, 1978, undated (Box 20)
  - Tuskegee airmen, 1973, 1988-2000, 2008 (Box 20)
  - United States Army Air Forces, 1945, undated (Box 20)
  - Women, 1942, 2008 (Box 20)
- Digital files
  - Interviews and related material
    - Adams, Susan, 2010 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_001
    - Allen, Hattie Mae Settles, 2008 (Container 1)*, mss_86243_145_003; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Banks, William S. M., 1997 (Container 1)*, mss_86243_145_004; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Barrett, Ogelsby B., 1998 (Container 1)*, mss_86243_145_006; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Blake, J. Herman, 2010 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_008
    - Burke, Albert, part 1, 1998, 2010 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_010
    - Burke, Albert, part 2, 1998, 2010 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_012
    - Cunningham, Leonard, 2008 (Container 1)*, mss_86243_145_013; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Dix, Roland, part 1, 1998 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_014
    - Dix, Roland, part 2, 1998 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_015
    - Dix, Roland, part 3, 1998 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_016
    - Earl, Ruth, part 1, (Container 1)*, mss_86243_145_018; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Earl, Ruth, part 2, (Container 1)*, mss_86243_145_019; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Fletcher, Howard, 2010 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_020
    - Goodwin, Arthur, part 1, 1998 (Container 1)*, mss_86243_145_023; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Goodwin, Arthur, part 2, 1998 (Container 1)*, mss_86243_145_022; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Goodwin, Felix, part 1, 1998 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_024
    - Goodwin, Felix, part 2, 1998 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_025
    - Goodwin, Felix, part 3, 1998 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_026
    - Goodwin, Felix, part 4, 1998 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_027
    - Goodwin, Felix, part 5, 1998 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_028
    - Goodwin, Felix, part 6, 1998 (Container 1), mss_86243_145_029
    - Green, Allen E., 1998 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_030
    - Hairston, Anna, 2010 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_032
    - Hairston, Joseph, part 1, 1998, 2010 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_033
    - Hairston, Joseph, part 2, 1998, 2010 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_034
    - Hairston, Joseph, part 3, 1998, 2010 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_035
    - Hairston, Joseph, part 4, 1998, 2010 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_036
    - Hairston, Joseph, part 5, 1998, 2010 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_037
    - Hanson, Charles, part 1, 1997 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_039; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hanson, Charles, part 2, 1997 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_040; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hanson, Charles, part 3, 1997 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_041; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hanson, Charles, part 4, 1997 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_042; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Harrod, Dennette Arthur, part 1, 1998 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_043
    - Harrod, Dennette Arthur, part 2, 1998 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_044
    - Harrod, Dennette Arthur, part 3, 1998 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_045
    - Harrod, Dennette Arthur, part 4, 1998 (Container 2), mss_86243_145_046
    - Hartsfield, Arnett, part 1, 1997 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_047; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hartsfield, Arnett, part 2, 1997 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_048; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hartsfield, Arnett, part 3, 1997 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_049; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.
    - Hartsfield, Arnett, part 4, 1997 (Container 2)*, mss_86243_145_050; * No documentation received by the Library granting release of interview.